They are the most dangerous killers on the planet. But this is not our planet.
Predators is a science fiction, action, thriller film directed by Nimród Antal.
A group of cold-blooded killers find themselves trapped on an alien
planet to be hunted by extraterrestrial Predators.
Royce, played by Adrien Brody.
Edwin, played by Topher Grace.
Isabelle, played by Alice Braga.
Stans, played by Walton Goggins.
Nikolai, played by Oleg Taktarov.
Noland, played by Laurence Fishburne.
Predators is a 2010 American science fiction action film directed by
Nimród Antal and written by Alex Litvak and Michael Finch.
It is the third installment in the Predator franchise.
The film features an ensemble cast, including Adrien Brody, Topher
Grace, Alice Braga, Walton Goggins, and Laurence Fishburne.
The plot follows a group of proficient killers who have been abducted and placed on a planet inhabited by
extraterrestrial trophy hunters, leading them to try to survive and look for a way back to Earth.
Producer Robert Rodriguez had developed a script for a third installment as early as 1994 after seeing the
original film, although it was not until 2009 that 20th Century Fox greenlit the project.
According to Rodriguez, the title Predators is an
allusion to the film Aliens (1986).
The title also has a double meaning, referring both to the extraterrestrial Predator
hunters and to the group of human characters who are pitted against them.
Filming took place in locations including Hawaii and Austin,
Texas from September 2009 and lasted 53 days.
Predators was released in the United States on
July 9, 2010, by 20th Century Fox.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $127
million against a $40 million budget.
A fourth film, The Predator, was released in 2018, and
a prequel, Prey, was released in 2022.
The film explores themes of hunter, predator, yakuza, alien life-form, sequel.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.